<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jessore Tourism</string>

    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome to jessore tourism. Here you will find the most attractive
        places you can plan a trip to. </string>

    <string name="button_text">Let\'s go</string>

    <string name="desc_dhopakhola">Dhopakhola village is situated in the Jessore Sadar Upozilla
        and it positions with an honored of its valiant descendant of freedom war. A mass momentous 
        in Dhopakhola approximately thirty people surrendered their survives aimed at the motherland. 
        The aforementioned has an archive for the sacrifices entitled ‘Shaheed Smrity Pathagar’ and 
        alternative one known as ‘Dhopakhola Cattra Maytri Pathagar’ recognized through the young, 
        spirited and supreme body fluid, Md Momin Uddin, an innovator of them is an undergraduate 
        of Business Studies Faculty from Dhaka University.</string>

    <string name="desc_balia_vakutia">Village named Balia Vakutia is famed for its minor intertwining 
        production (materialize), wherever Shari, Lounge, Gamcha and many more. Dresses are manufactured.</string>
    
    <string name="desc_rampur">Rampur village has turned out to be a tourist charm intended for its 
        island-like appearance bordered by twofold rivers which are named Jhapa Bayor as well as 
        Khajura Bayor. The Kopotakkho River tides over the place.</string>
    
    <string name="desc_abhaynagar">There a small village named Dhoolgaam once had a wonderful multifaceted 
        of 17 Hindu sanctuaries but merely single remains currently. Most of the sanctuaries were damaged 
        through the Bhairab River.</string>
    
    <string name="desc_sagardari">In Sagardari village of Jessore, the house of Michael Madhusudan Dutta 
        is situated. Now it’s a museum. Visitors can visit here and can learn more about the great Bangladeshi poet.</string>
    
    <string name="desc_vaatnogor">In Vaatnogor, relics of eleven sanctuaries multifaceted, enthusiastic 
        to Lord shiva’s period. It keeps the glorious past of Bangla.</string>
    
    <string name="desc_shahi_mosque">it is situated in Hamidpur village which is an illustration of
        Muslim Sultani era. Visitors can come here and also can say their prayers.</string>

    <string name="desc_imam_bara">It is an ancient building which was made by Hazi Muhammad Mohsin 
        and it is situated beside the Dhaka-Khulna Highway.</string>
    
    <string name="desc_airport">Jessore airport is an international airport. Here foreigners can come from abroad.</string>
    
    <string name="desc_benapole">Benapole is a boundary city in Bangladesh, the furthermost frequently 
        used border when roaming in the middle of Kolkata in addition to Dhaka. The Indian on the side is known as Haridaspur.</string>
    
    <string name="desc_mallinath">A terracotta inscription bearing the spitting image of Mallinath,
        a woman tirthankar (saint) of the Jain religious conviction, was bring into being at the Embankment
        of Dam Dam Peer in Manirampur Upazila which is 1800 years old.</string>
</resources>
